Guide to the Emilie F. Miller papers, 1987-1991
George Mason University Libraries
- Emilie F.Miller Collection
  - Transfer Development Rights and Land Use Study [4 of 7] 1988 - 1992 (Folder 13, Box 23)
  - Transfer Development Rights and Land Use Study [5 of 7] 1988 - 1992 (Folder 14, Box 23)
  - Transfer Development Rights and Land Use Study [6 of 7] 1988 - 1992 (Folder 15, Box 23)
  - Transfer Development Rights and Land Use Study [7 of 7] 1988 - 1992 (Folder 16, Box 23)
  - Tree Study 1988 - 1989 (Folder 17, Box 23)
  - Vehicles Powered by Clean Transportation Fuels Study Committee -HJR 113 [1 of 8] (Folder 18, Box 23)
  - Vehicles Powered by Clean Transportation Fuels Study Committee - HJR 113 [2 of 8] (Folder 19, Box 23)
  - Vehicles Powered by Clean Transportation Fuels Study Committee - HJR 113 [3 of 8] (Folder 20, Box 23)
  - Vehicles Powered by Clean Transportation Fuels Study Committee - HJR 113 [4 of 8] (Folder 21, Box 23)
  - Vehicles Powered by Clean Transportation Fuels Study Committee - HJR 113 [5 of 8] (Folder 22, Box 23)
  - Vehicles Powered by Clean Transportation Fuels Study Committee - HJR 113 [6 of 8] (Folder 23, Box 23)
  - Vehicles Powered by Clean Transportation Fuels Study Committee - HJR 113 [7 of 8] (Folder 24, Box 23)
  - Vehicles Powered by Clean Transportation Fuels Study Committee - HJR 113 [8 of 8] (Folder 25, Box 23)
  - State Joint Resolution 52 - Abuse in Facilities for the Mentally Disabled, Report -88 carry over. 1988- 1989 (Folder 1, Box 24)
  - Bills and Resolutions [Control Lists] 1989 (Folder 2, Box 24)
  - State Bill 573 - Board of Rehabilitative Service 1989 (Folder 3, Box 24)
  - SJR 37 - Social Service Paying FICA [1 of 3] 1988 - 1989 (Folder 4, Box 24)
  - SJR 37 - Social Service Paying FICA [2 of 3] 1988 - 1989 (Folder 5, Box 24)
  - SJR 37 - Social Service Paying FICA [3 of 3] 1988 - 1989 (Folder 6, Box 24)
  - Civil Penalties for Zoning Violations [SB-527] 1989 (Folder 7, Box 24)
  - State Joint Resolution - 123, Commending Fairfax County Council of Arts 1989 (Folder 8, Box 24)
  - State Joint Resolution - 153, Commending Louis Ray Volrath 1989 (Folder 9, Box 24)
  - State Joint Resolution- 49,Eliminate Exemption of Commercial Zone Motor Carrier (Folder 10, Box 24)
  - State Bill 718, Emergency Absentee Ballot 1989 (Folder 11, Box 24)
  - State Bill 715, Exceptions to the Residential Landlord Acts 1989 (Folder 12, Box 24)
  - State Bill 714, Exceptions to Residential Landlord Tenant Act 1989 (Folder 13, Box 24)
  - State Bill 596, Extended School Day Programs [1 of 2] 1989 (Folder 14, Box 24)
  - State Bill 596, Extended School Day Programs [2 of 2] 1989 (Folder 15, Box 24)
  - State Bill 571, Fairfax City Building and Fire Regulation 1989 (Folder 16, Box 24)
  - 1989 SJR-130, Incentives for Consolidating School Functions 1989 (Folder 17, Box 24)
  - 1989 SB-719,In Person Absentee Ballot Deadline 1989 (Folder 18, Box 24)
  - 1989 SB-535, Organizations Exempt from Property Tax [Inova Services Inc.] 1989 (Folder 19, Box 24)
  - 1989 SB-597, Precluding Death Penalty for Mentally Retarded [1 of 3] 1989 (Folder 20, Box 24)
  - 1989 SB-597, Precluding Death Penalty for Mentally Retarded [2 of 3] 1989 (Folder 21, Box 24)
  - 1989 SB-597, Precluding Death Penalty for Mentally Retarded [3 of 3] 1989 (Folder 22, Box 24)
  - HJR- 164, Restroom Equity 1989 (Folder 23, Box 24)
  - 1989 SB-598, Rights of Patients and Residents of Mentally Retarded 1989 (Folder 24, Box 24)
  - 1989 SB-471, School Board Date of Appointment 1989 (Folder 25, Box 24)
  - 1989 SB-572, School Capital Expenditure Financing 1989 (Folder 26, Box 24)
  - 1989 SB-717,Selection for Jury Duty 1989 (Folder 27, Box 24)
  - SB-64, Blake Lane 1989 (Folder 28, Box 24)
  - SB-64, Property Tax 1989 (Folder 29, Box 24)
  - SJR -37, Study on Impact of Social Security Tax by Local Social Service Agents on Behalf of Homemaker and Companion Workers 1988 (Folder 30, Box 24)
  - SJR-54, Doug Walker Commemorative 1989 (Folder 31, Box 24)
  - 1989 SB-794, Subdivision and Site Plan 1989 (Folder 32, Box 24)
  - 1989 SB-691,Taxes 1989 (Folder 33, Box 24)
  - 1989 SJR-152,Thomas Jefferson High School [1 of 4] 1989 (Folder 34, Box 24)
  - 1989 SJR-152,Thomas Jefferson High School [2 of 4] 1989 (Folder 35, Box 24)
  - 1989 SJR-152,Thomas Jefferson High School [3 of 4] 1989 (Folder 36, Box 24)
  - 1989 SJR-152,Thomas Jefferson High School [4 of 4] 1989 (Folder 37, Box 24)
  - 1989 SJR-138, Mental Health,Mental Retarded and Substance Abuse Services - Training 1989 (Folder 38, Box 24)
  - 1989 SB-716, Violations by Landlords [Penalties] 1989 (Folder 39, Box 24)
  - 1989 SB-793, Virginia Alcohol Safety Action Program 1989 (Folder 40, Box 24)
  - 1989 SJR-151, Women's History Month 1989 (Folder 41, Box 24)
  - 1989 Senate Resolution -45, Death of Maureen V.O'Donnell 1989 (Folder 42, Box 24)
  - SJR-109, Honoring George Snyder 1989 (Folder 43, Box 24)
  - SJR-101, March as Women;s History Month-VA 1988 (Folder 44, Box 24)
  - SB-63, Repeal of Adv. of Dept for Development of Disabled 1989 (Folder 45, Box 24)
  - SB-50, Funding State Board [MHMRSAS- 6 year Plan] 1989 (Folder 46, Box 24)
  - SB-243, Economic Development Authority [Commission Enlargement -E.D.Rose] 1989 (Folder 47, Box 24)
  - SJR-52, Study Criminal Prosecution of Persons who Abuse Mentally Retarded 1989 (Folder 48, Box 24)
  - Senate Bill -64, Blake Lane 1989 (Folder 49, Box 24)
  - SB-129, Advertising by Licensed Facilities or Institutions for Mentally ill/Retarded 1990 (Folder 1, Box 25)
  - SJR-22, Alternative Psychiatric and Drug Treatment Levels -Insurance Coverage 1990 (Folder 2, Box 25)
  - Bills - for Other State Funded Clearing Houses (Folder 3, Box 25)
  - Bills Resolution Tracking (Folder 4, Box 25)
  - Budget Amendments (Folder 5, Box 25)
  - Budget Amendment Staffing Mental Retarded Training Centers 1990 (Folder 6, Box 25)
  - Chief Patron Report [1 of 3] (Folder 7, Box 25)
  - Chief Patron Report [2 of 3] (Folder 8, Box 25)
  - Chief Patron Report [3 of 3] (Folder 9, Box 25)
  - SB-301, Civil Penalties for Violations of Zoning Ordinances 1990 (Folder 10, Box 25)
  - Co-Patron Bills [1 of 2] 1988 (Folder 11, Box 25)
  - Co-Patron Bills [2 of 2] 1988 (Folder 12, Box 25)
  - S.B.-303 1990 Cosmotology ,Definition of [1 of 3] 1990 (Folder 14, Box 25)
  - S.B.-303 1990 Cosmotology ,Definition of [2 of 3] 1990 (Folder 15, Box 25)
  - S.B.-303 1990 Cosmotology ,Definition of [3 of 3] 1990 (Folder 16, Box 25)
  - S.J.R- 121 ,Earth Day 1990 (Folder 17, Box 25)
  - S.J.R.- 119, Family Support Services Study 1990 (Folder 18, Box 25)
  - S.J.R. - Frank Crosby ,International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers Local 26 1990 (Folder 19, Box 25)
  - Graphic of Clearing House Growth (Folder 20, Box 25)
  - Senate Resolution - James Weiss Jefferson High School 1990 (Folder 21, Box 25)
  - Emilie F. Miller Legislation Public Facilities 1990 (Folder 22, Box 25)
  - MHANV Board Members Self Help Advisory Council Members 1990 (Folder 23, Box 25)
  - NCSL Committee on Human Services 1990 (Folder 24, Box 25)
  - New Self Help Groups Addendum to Directory 1990 (Folder 25, Box 25)
  - S.J.R.- 148 Northern Virginia Youth Symphony Association 1990 (Folder 26, Box 25)
  - State Bill - 139, Optometrists 1990 (Folder 27, Box 25)
  - State Bill-302, Prescription of Drugs by Certain Practitioners 1990 (Folder 28, Box 25)
  - State Bill -41, Property Tax Exemption ,Northern Virginia Family Services,Inc. 1990 (Folder 29, Box 25)
  - State Bill-475, Programs Outside School Hours [Extended Day Care] [1 of 3] 1990 (Folder 30, Box 25)
  - State Bill-475, Programs Outside School Hours [Extended Day Care] [2 of 3] 1990 (Folder 31, Box 25)
  - State Bill-475, Programs Outside School Hours [Extended Day Care] [3 of 3] 1990 (Folder 32, Box 25)
  - S.B.-111, Regulation of Child Care Services and Facilities in Certain Countries and Cities 1990 (Folder 33, Box 25)
  - Revised Proposal 1990 (Folder 34, Box 25)
  - Research and Statistics ,N.Y 1990 (Folder 35, Box 25)
  - Self Help Articles and Self Help Newsletter 1990 (Folder 36, Box 25)
  - Self Help ClearingHouse File [Mental Health Association of Northern Virginia] 1990 (Folder 37, Box 25)
  - S.J.R.-120, Study Self Help Group Clearing House 1990 (Folder 38, Box 25)
  - State Bill 210, Sentencing in Capital Murder Cases Mental Retardation [1 of 2] 1990 (Folder 39, Box 25)
  - State Bill 210, Sentencing in Capital Murder Cases Mental Retardation [2 of 2] 1990 (Folder 40, Box 25)
  - State Bill 476, Sentencing Proceedings -Capital Cases [1 of 2] 1990 (Folder 41, Box 25)
  - State Bill 476, Sentencing Proceedings -Capital Cases [2 of 2] 1990 (Folder 42, Box 25)
  - Virginia Women's History Month 1990 (Folder 43, Box 25)
  - Women in Politics Center 1990 (Folder 44, Box 25)
  - Women in Military Service Memorial 1990 (Folder 45, Box 25)
  - S.J.R- 206, Alternative Fuels Pilot Projects 1991 (Folder 1, Box 26)
  - State Bill - 526, ARC Property Tax Exemption 1991 (Folder 2, Box 26)
  - State Bill -669, Authority to Cut Grass Fairfax County 1991 (Folder 3, Box 26)
  - Chief Patron Report 1991 (Folder 4, Box 26)
  - City of Fairfax Parking Authority 1991 (Folder 5, Box 26)
  - Commending Resolution -1991 [1 of 4] 1991 (Folder 6, Box 26)
  - Commending Resolution -1991 [2 of 4] 1991 (Folder 7, Box 26)
  - Commending Resolution -1991 [3 of 4] 1991 (Folder 8, Box 26)
  - Commending Resolution -1991 [4 of 4] 1991 (Folder 9, Box 26)
  - S.J.R.- 211, Commending Thomas Jefferson High School 1991 (Folder 10, Box 26)
  - State Bill- 668, CSB Procurement Act Exemption 1991 (Folder 11, Box 26)
  - S.J.R- 122, Consolidating Licensing Functions Within Health and Human Resources Secretariat 1991 (Folder 12, Box 26)
  - State Bill - 696, Cosmotology 1991 (Folder 13, Box 26)
  - State Bill -820, Deemed Consent for HIV Testing 1991 (Folder 14, Box 26)
  - State Bill - 642, Election Results and Procedures After Polls Close 1991 (Folder 15, Box 26)
  - State Bill -507, Exemption for Non-Profit Groups 1991 (Folder 16, Box 26)
  - 1991 State Bill, 1990 S.B.-475, Extended Day Care [1 of 5] 1991 (Folder 17, Box 26)
  - 1991 State Bill, 1990 S.B.-475, Extended Day Care [2 of 5] 1991 (Folder 18, Box 26)
  - 1991 State Bill, 1990 S.B.-475, Extended Day Care [3 of 5] 1991 (Folder 19, Box 26)
  - 1991 State Bill, 1990 S.B.-475, Extended Day Care [4 of 5] 1991 (Folder 20, Box 26)
  - 1991 State Bill, 1990 S.B.-475, Extended Day Care [5 of 5] 1991 (Folder 21, Box 26)
  - Extended Day Care Bill Support File 1991 (Folder 22, Box 26)
  - Information on 1991 State Bills and House Bills 1991 (Folder 23, Box 26)
  - State Bill - 695, Informed Consent [Peanut Bill -II] 1991 (Folder 24, Box 26)
  - State Bill - 542, Jewish Community Foundation Property Tax Exemption 1991 (Folder 25, Box 26)
  - Legislation - 1990 Carry Over 1991 (Folder 26, Box 26)
  - 1991 Emilie F. Miller Legislation Tracking Forms 1991 (Folder 27, Box 26)
  - Legislative Services 1991 (Folder 28, Box 26)
  - S.J.R.- 208, Music in our Schools Month March, 1991 (Folder 29, Box 26)
  - State Bill- 641, Notice of Candidacy and Required Filings 1991 (Folder 30, Box 26)
  - House Bill - 424, Peanut Bill-I [1 of 6] 1991 (Folder 31, Box 26)
  - House Bill - 424, Peanut Bill-I [2 of 6] 1991 (Folder 32, Box 26)
  - House Bill - 424, Peanut Bill-I [3 of 6] 1991 (Folder 33, Box 26)
  - House Bill - 424, Peanut Bill-I [4 of 6] 1991 (Folder 34, Box 26)
  - House Bill - 424, Peanut Bill-I [5 of 6] 1991 (Folder 35, Box 26)
  - House Bill - 424, Peanut Bill-I [6 of 6] 1991 (Folder 36, Box 26)
  - State Bill - 543, Removal of Unsafe Vehicles, City of Fairfax 1991 (Folder 37, Box 26)
  - S.J.R.- 51, Regulating Marriage and Family Therapists study 1991 (Folder 38, Box 26)
  - Restoration of Private School Funding - Fairfax County 1991 (Folder 39, Box 26)
  - Schedule Resolution -1991 1991 (Folder 40, Box 26)
  - Temporary Employment Agencies, Tennessee 1991 (Folder 41, Box 26)
  - S.J.R.- 247, Virginia Earth Day April 21, 1991 (Folder 42, Box 26)
  - S.J.R.- 216, Virginia Women's History Month March, 1991 (Folder 43, Box 26)
  - S.J.R. - 200, Special Education [1 of 7] 1989 (Folder 44, Box 26)
  - S.J.R. - 200, Special Education [2 of 7] 1989 (Folder 45, Box 26)
  - S.J.R. - 200, Special Education [3 of 7] 1989 (Folder 46, Box 26)
  - S.J.R. - 200, Special Education [4 of 7] 1989 (Folder 47, Box 26)
  - S.J.R. - 200, Special Education [5 of 7] 1989 (Folder 48, Box 26)
  - S.J.R. - 200, Special Education [6 of 7] 1989 (Folder 49, Box 26)
  - S.J.R. - 200, Special Education [7 of 7] 1989 (Folder 50, Box 26)
  - Emilie F. Miller Ads-1987 1987 (Folder 1, Box 27)
  - Campaign 1988-1991 1988- 1991 (Folder 2, Box 27)
  - Campaign in the 90's -The New Inexpensive Alternative to Television 1990 (Folder 3, Box 27)
  - Emilie F. Miller - 5min Tape (Folder 4, Box 27)
  - Campaign Literature -Other Candidates in 1987 [1 of 4] 1987 (Folder 5, Box 27)
  - Campaign Literature -Other Candidates in 1987 [2 of 4] 1987 (Folder 6, Box 27)
  - Campaign Literature -Other Candidates in 1987 [3 of 4] 1987 (Folder 7, Box 27)
  - Campaign Literature -Other Candidates in 1987 [4 of 4] 1987 (Folder 8, Box 27)
  - Campaign Materials -1987 [1 of 4] 1987 (Folder 9, Box 27)
  - Campaign Materials -1987 [2 of 4] 1987 (Folder 10, Box 27)
  - Campaign Materials -1987 [3 of 4] 1987 (Folder 11, Box 27)
  - Campaign Materials -1987 [4 of 4] 1987 (Folder 12, Box 27)
  - Campaign Prospectus (Folder 13, Box 27)
  - Campaign Staff (Folder 14, Box 27)
  - Candidates and Campaigns -1987 1987 (Folder 15, Box 27)
  - City of Fairfax Future Land Use (Folder 16, Box 27)
  - Democrat Newsletter (Folder 17, Box 27)
  - Democratic Party of Virginia (Folder 18, Box 27)
  - Editorials and Columns (Folder 19, Box 27)
  - EFM - Endorsements 1987 (Folder 20, Box 27)
  - EFM - Issues in 1987 1987 (Folder 21, Box 27)
  - Strategy in 1987-EFM 1987 (Folder 22, Box 27)
  - Fundraising - Caterers 1987 (Folder 23, Box 27)
  - EFM - Fund Raiser 1987 (Folder 24, Box 27)
  - Georgette Klinger Inc. 1987 (Folder 25, Box 27)
  - John Milliken 1987 (Folder 26, Box 27)
  - Joint Brochure and Other Literature 1987 (Folder 27, Box 27)
  - Junior League of Virginia 1987 (Folder 28, Box 27)
  - Kaiser Permanente Center - Philip Marstiller [Correspondence] 1987 (Folder 29, Box 27)
  - Kennedy Library Foundation 1987 (Folder 30, Box 27)
  - Kentucky Colonels 1987 (Folder 31, Box 27)
  - King's Dominion 1991 (Folder 32, Box 27)
  - The League of Women Voters of Virginia, Virginia Legislative Directory General Assembly 1990-1991 (Folder 33, Box 27)
  - General Assembly of Virginia Senate Members -1990 1990 (Folder 34, Box 27)
  - Virginia Legislative Directory 1990 (Folder 35, Box 27)
  - S.J.R. - 48,29,59 Resolutions in Senate (Folder 36, Box 27)
  - Larsen,Larry - Northern Virginia Delegation [Correspondence] 1988 (Folder 1, Box 28)
  - Lazarus at the Gate (Folder 2, Box 28)
  - League of Women Voters - Mental Health Study (Folder 3, Box 28)
  - Lee Highway Widening Plan (Folder 4, Box 28)
  - Lee Highway - Correspondence Perkins (Folder 5, Box 28)
  - Lee Highway Thompson Family Cemetery (Folder 6, Box 28)
  - Legal Secretaries (Folder 7, Box 28)
  - Lemon Law (Folder 8, Box 28)
  - [Correspondence with Mary Sue Terry and Gerald L. Bailes] (Folder 9, Box 28)
  - Letters -- Newly Registered Voters March, 1988 (Folder 10, Box 28)
  - Letter to Fairfax City, Newspaper Clippings (Folder 11, Box 28)
  - Mailing List Systems (Folder 12, Box 28)
  - Mantua Precinct Letters 1991- S.B. general Registrar 1991 (Folder 13, Box 28)
  - Metro Application (Folder 14, Box 28)
  - Miller for Senate Campaign Budget (Folder 15, Box 28)
  - Miller for State Senate Fundraising Events - 1987 Originals 1987 (Folder 16, Box 28)
  - Miller on Issues -1987 1987 (Folder 17, Box 28)
  - Petitions (Folder 18, Box 28)
  - Phone Bank and Instructions Scripts (Folder 19, Box 28)
  - Poll (Folder 20, Box 28)
  - Pre-Election Coverage (Folder 21, Box 28)
  - Press Releases (Folder 22, Box 28)
  - Questionnaires - 1987 (Folder 23, Box 28)
  - Republican Candidates (Folder 24, Box 28)
  - EFM - Resume (Folder 25, Box 28)
  - Return for Files Treasurer (Folder 26, Box 28)
  - Election - 1987 Recount 1987 (Folder 27, Box 28)
  - Signs - Permit and Locations (Folder 28, Box 28)
  - The FireBird Ball -1990 1990 (Folder 29, Box 28)
  - The Democratic Publication Campaign Kick Off (Folder 30, Box 28)
  - Underdog Fund (Folder 31, Box 28)
  - Virginia Senate -1986 1986 (Folder 32, Box 28)
  - Virginia Trial Lawyers Association (Folder 33, Box 28)
  - Virginia Victory Group (Folder 34, Box 28)
  - Virginia Pilot Poll (Folder 35, Box 28)
  - Volunteer Booklet and Forms (Folder 36, Box 28)
  - Volunteer Lists (Folder 37, Box 28)
  - Voter Statistics (Folder 38, Box 28)
  - Volunteer -Students Certificate (Folder 39, Box 28)
  - Women Campaign Fund (Folder 40, Box 28)
  - Women's National Democratic Club (Folder 41, Box 28)
  - Abortion Rights [Campaign] (Folder 1, Box 29)
  - EFM - ADS (Folder 2, Box 29)
  - An Evening to Honor Two Great Senators- Emilie F. Miller and Senator Al Gore Jr (Folder 3, Box 29)
  - Campaign in 1991 1991 (Folder 4, Box 29)
  - Campaign - Administration (Folder 5, Box 29)
  - Campaign Chronicle for the Friends of Emilie F. Miller (Folder 6, Box 29)
  - Campaign Donations (Folder 7, Box 29)
  - Campaign Materials- 1991 [1 of 4] 1991 (Folder 8, Box 29)
  - Campaign Materials- 1991 [2 of 4] 1991 (Folder 9, Box 29)
  - Campaign Materials- 1991 [3 of 4] 1991 (Folder 10, Box 29)
  - Campaign Materials- 1991 [4 of 4] 1991 (Folder 11, Box 29)
  - Campaign Materials 1991 (Folder 12, Box 29)
  - Campaign Plan: Budget (Folder 13, Box 29)
  - Campaign Response (Folder 14, Box 29)
  - Candidacy for Re-Election (Folder 15, Box 29)
  - Candidate Filing Forms (Folder 16, Box 29)
  - Charette Mark (Folder 17, Box 29)
  - Choice Issues (Folder 18, Box 29)
  - Citizens for Balanced Growth PAC (Folder 19, Box 29)
  - 1991 Correspondence- not Answerable (Folder 20, Box 29)
  - Dental Hygienists Association (Folder 21, Box 29)
  - Door-to-Door Campaign 1991 1991 (Folder 22, Box 29)
  - Right to Education - Letter 1991 (Folder 23, Box 29)
  - Educators, Retired List and Letter 1991 (Folder 24, Box 29)
  - Election Publications 1991 (Folder 25, Box 29)
  - Emily List- A List for Democratic Women 1991 (Folder 26, Box 29)
  - E.F.M. Research: CTTEE on Local Government 1991 1991 (Folder 27, Box 29)
  - E.F.M Research: CTTEE on General Laws 1991 1991 (Folder 28, Box 29)
  - E.F.M Research: CTTEE on Education and Health 1991 1991 (Folder 29, Box 29)
  - E.F.M Research: CTTEE on Rehabilitation and Social Services 1991 1991 (Folder 30, Box 29)
  - Emilie's Voting Record (Folder 31, Box 29)
  - Endorsements - EFM (Folder 32, Box 29)
  - Voting Summary of key Environmental Legislation 1991 (Folder 33, Box 29)
  - Fairfax City 1989- 1991 (Folder 1, Box 30)
  - Fairfax County Democratic Committee 1991 (Folder 2, Box 30)
  - Fairfax County Events 1991 (Folder 3, Box 30)
  - Fairfax Medical Society Gala 1991 (Folder 4, Box 30)
  - Finance - Miscellaneous 1991 (Folder 5, Box 30)
  - First Fund Raising Letter to Constituents whom Emilie Miller Helped 1991 (Folder 6, Box 30)
  - Fund Raising Campaign 1991 (Folder 7, Box 30)
  - Introductory Letter to New Precincts [Marshall and Lincolnia 1991] 1991 (Folder 8, Box 30)
  - Letters - 1991 [1 of 2] 1991 (Folder 9, Box 30)
  - Letters - 1991 [2 of 2] 1991 (Folder 10, Box 30)
  - Mental Health 1991 (Folder 11, Box 30)
  - Mothers and Majority Leaders - Celebrating the roles of women in society 1991 (Folder 12, Box 30)
  - Originals- Effectiveness Record 1991 (Folder 13, Box 30)
  - General Survey's [Miscellaneous] 1991 (Folder 14, Box 30)
  - Petitions Filled - Notarized 1991 (Folder 15, Box 30)
  - Petitions - Originals 1991 (Folder 16, Box 30)
  - Polling - Campaign '91 1991 (Folder 17, Box 30)
  - Polling Phases Information 1991 (Folder 18, Box 30)
  - Press Clips and News Letter 1991 (Folder 19, Box 30)
  - Precinct Information 1991 (Folder 20, Box 30)
  - Press Release - 1991 1991 (Folder 21, Box 30)
  - Questionnaires or Survey - TBC Dated Materials 1991 (Folder 22, Box 30)
  - Questionnaires - 1991 [1 of 3] 1991 (Folder 23, Box 30)
  - Questionnaires - 1991 [2 of 3] 1991 (Folder 24, Box 30)
  - Questionnaires - 1991 [3 of 3] 1991 (Folder 25, Box 30)
  - Radio Recordings of Emilie F. Miller, "With all that goes on at the State Capital" 1991 (Folder 26, Box 30)
  - Statistical Data - 1991 (Folder 27, Box 30)
  - Volunteer Meetings - March,1991 March, 1991 (Folder 28, Box 30)
  - Voting Statistics - 1991 1991 (Folder 29, Box 30)
  - Women Campaign Conference 1991 (Folder 30, Box 30)
  - Women's Group Lists 1991 (Folder 31, Box 30)
  - Women's Fund Raiser for Emilie F. Miller 1991 (Folder 32, Box 30)
  - Coalition Community Services Board (Folder 1, Box 31)
  - Coalition:Department for Rights of Virginians with Disabilities (Folder 2, Box 31)
  - Coalition for Mentally Disabled Citizens of Virginia (Folder 3, Box 31)
  - Coalition Steering Committee Meeting (Folder 4, Box 31)
  - Coalition for MDC of Virginia (Folder 5, Box 31)
  - Coalition for MDC - Final Bill Disposition '93 (Folder 6, Box 31)
  - Coalition for MDC -Consortium for Citizens with Disabilities (Folder 7, Box 31)
  - Coalition for MDC - State Comprehensive Plan (Folder 8, Box 31)
  - Coalition for MDC - Special Education Programs (Folder 9, Box 31)
  - Coalition for MDC - Virginia Mental Health Consumers Association (Folder 10, Box 31)
  - Coalition for MDC -Regional Focus Meetings (Folder 11, Box 31)
  - Coalition for MDC - Mental Health News (Folder 12, Box 31)
  - Coalition for MDC -Northern Virginia Mental Health Institute Advisory Committee (Folder 13, Box 31)
  - Coalition for MDC -Roster of Community Services Board 1992-1993 (Folder 14, Box 31)
  - Coalition for MDC -Plan's and Future (Folder 15, Box 31)
  - Coalition for Virginia Board for People with Disabilities '93 (Folder 16, Box 31)
  - Coalition for MDC -Steering Committee Meetings (Folder 17, Box 31)
  - Coalition for MDC - Emilie Miller Record '89-'91 (Folder 18, Box 31)
  - Coalition for MDC -Summit Meetings and Alliance for Mentally Ill - AMI (Folder 19, Box 31)
  - Coalition for MDC - Summary of Budget Recommendations (Folder 20, Box 31)
  - Coalition for MDC - Memorandum,Letters (Folder 21, Box 31)
  - Coalition: CSB New Initiative Services Implementation Schedule Summary [1 of 2] (Folder 22, Box 31)
  - Coalition: CSB New Initiative Services Implementation Schedule Summary [2 of 2] (Folder 23, Box 31)
  - Coalition for MDC - Report on Implementation and Effects of 1988-1990 Community Services Initiative (Folder 24, Box 31)
  - Coalition for MDC - Public Hearing Schedule Licensure Regulation Revision (Folder 25, Box 31)
  - Coalition for MDC - Actual Fiscal 93 Revenues, Economy and Implications (Folder 26, Box 31)
  - Coalition for MDC -Correspondence (Folder 27, Box 31)
  - Coalition for MDC -Disability Related Bills (Folder 28, Box 31)
  - Coalition for MDC-Operational Details of Coalition (Folder 29, Box 31)
  - Coalition for MDC - Advocating and Building Coalitions for the Decade, Speech by Gov. J. Baliles (Folder 30, Box 31)
  - Coalition for MDC -Coalition Buddy System (Folder 31, Box 31)
  - Coalition for MDC -Community Funding Initiative Report (Folder 32, Box 31)
  - Coalition for MDC - Alliance for Mentally Ill rally and other Correspondence (Folder 33, Box 31)
  - Coalition for MDC -Mental Health Association, Annual Legislative Briefing (Folder 34, Box 31)
  - Coalition for MDC -Proposals (Folder 35, Box 31)
  - Coalition for MDC - Miscellaneous Papers (Folder 36, Box 31)
  - Photographs Collection December, 1987 (Folder 1, Box 32)
  - Addresses,Cards,Phone Message (Folder 2, Box 32)
  - Invitations - '91 1991 (Folder 3, Box 32)
  - Resume - Emilie F. Miller 1991 (Folder 4, Box 32)